<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nz.js(con);</title>
    <description>nz.js(con); is New Zealand's dedicated national JavaScript conference. It has an open CFP, low cost of entry, and broad variety of JS related topics. It will be held on March 9th &amp; 10th in 2017, at Shed 6 in Wellington, New Zealand.
</description>
    <link>/2017/</link>
    <atom:link href="/2017/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 10:15:44 +1200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 10:15:44 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>2018 and beyond</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The conference was &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/JavaScript-NZ/Society-Meetings/issues/35&quot;&gt;always conceived&lt;/a&gt; as having a rotating set of locations and organisers. Are &lt;strong&gt;you&lt;/strong&gt; keen to be an organiser for &lt;strong&gt;nz.js(con); 2018&lt;/strong&gt; with the support of the &lt;strong&gt;nz.js();&lt;/strong&gt; committee? We’ve put together an application process for you to step up to run the conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/forms/9O6bt3gXXRuI2FGQ2&quot;&gt;Apply to run&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;nz.js(con); 2018&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Read more about &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/JavaScript-NZ/Society-Meetings/issues/55&quot;&gt;why we’re doing this&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Learn about what’s involved in running an &lt;strong&gt;nz.js(con);&lt;/strong&gt; with &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/JavaScript-NZ/nzjscon-docs&quot;&gt;our detailed conference runner’s guide&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The application process closes on the &lt;strong&gt;23rd of April&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 08:39:55 +1200</pubDate>
        <link>/2017/conference/2017/04/02/2018-and-beyond.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2017/conference/2017/04/02/2018-and-beyond.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>conference</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Videos now up</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re a week on from the conference, and all the videos have been
up for a few days now! &lt;a href=&quot;/schedule&quot;&gt;Browse through the schedule&lt;/a&gt; to read talk
descriptions and jump over to the corresponding video, or just hop over to the
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLE58b5NgENKm3h5r2R17Q4ypZIGjDI4nl&quot;&gt;playlist on
YouTube&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are also photographs from the conference &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/4nitsirk/sets/72157681209112575/&quot;&gt;over on
Flickr&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A big thanks to all our speakers, workshop runners, volunteers, and attendees
that helped to make the conference a memorable one!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Help us figure out what’s next for &lt;strong&gt;nz.js(con);&lt;/strong&gt; by contributing to the
discussion in &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/JavaScript-NZ/Society-Meetings/issues/55&quot;&gt;our society issues
register&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 09:39:55 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>/2017/conference/2017/03/18/videos-are-up.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2017/conference/2017/03/18/videos-are-up.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>conference</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thursday evening social event</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Rather than an afterparty, we have a room booked at &lt;a href=&quot;http://macsbrewbar.co.nz/&quot;&gt;Mac’s Brew
Bar&lt;/a&gt; (a very short walk from the venue) for
&lt;strong&gt;Thursday&lt;/strong&gt; evening. That’s to make it easy for out-of-towners to attend, and
also so you can catch up with new folks you meet the day after at the
conference. Matt McKegg aka &lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/destroy-with-science&quot;&gt;DESTROY WITH
SCIENCE&lt;/a&gt; will be providing the JS
powered music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a ‘buy-your-own-drinks’ event, but we’ll provide a few platters of nibbles
(with thanks to NEC for sponsoring some food).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;getting-to-the-conference&quot;&gt;Getting to the conference&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget you can find public transport directions to the venue &lt;a href=&quot;/venue-and-directions/&quot;&gt;over on the
venue page&lt;/a&gt; but also
we’ve set up &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1ZaFYoPoAxdjZKVNO-EyINGQNj98kJNxptehJxKZquBU/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;a ridesharing editable
spreadsheet&lt;/a&gt;
for those of you who are looking to organise between yourselves for a ride to or
from the conference.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 19:39:55 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>/2017/conference/2017/03/05/thursday-evening-social.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2017/conference/2017/03/05/thursday-evening-social.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>conference</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Call for volunteers</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As a community run conference, we rely on volunteers to help make the event a success. We’ve already had several lovely people volunteer — but &lt;strong&gt;we’re looking for a few more&lt;/strong&gt;, as many hands make light work!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular we could use a few more people at the registration desk throughout the conference, and possibly a few more session chairs (who introduce the speakers and keep the conference running on time).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re keen to pitch in, here’s what you need to know:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You &lt;strong&gt;must&lt;/strong&gt; be already attending the conference (this is a capacity limitation as we’re sold out).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Email &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nzjscon@gmail.com?subject=Volunteering&quot;&gt;nzjscon@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; with the subject line &lt;em&gt;‘Volunteering’&lt;/em&gt; so we can give you more info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;a-week-to-go&quot;&gt;A week to go&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re at max capacity so sorry there are &lt;em&gt;no tickets left&lt;/em&gt;. If you missed out
you can at least rest safe in the knowledge that we’re recording all conference
talks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ticket holders should look out for a few more annoucements (we’ll pop you an
email) before kick off time next week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 19:39:55 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>/2017/conference/2017/03/02/call-for-volunteers.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2017/conference/2017/03/02/call-for-volunteers.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>conference</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Node CTF</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re please to annouce that we’ve got another workshop available for conference
attendees:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by the KiwiCon badge challenge, &lt;strong&gt;nz.js(con);&lt;/strong&gt; will feature its own
CTF (capture-the-flag) challenge. Trapped in a submarine at the bottom of the
ocean, you must use your JavaScript wits to survive. Whether in teams or alone,
you will complete a series of puzzles as you try to get your ship operational.
Open to all skill levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the Thursday afternoon between lunch and afternoon tea, the middle room will
hold the workshop, which can support up to 50 participants. You don’t need to
sign up for this one, but you’ll need to bring your laptop along to participate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find out &lt;a href=&quot;/workshops/node-ctf/&quot;&gt;more about the Node CTF event here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;just-over-a-week-to-go&quot;&gt;Just over a week to go&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re sold out! We’re at max capacity so sorry there are &lt;em&gt;no tickets left&lt;/em&gt;. If you
missed out you can at least rest safe in the knowledge that we’re recording all
conference talks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ticket holders should look out for a few more annoucements (we’ll pop you an
email) before we get this thing rolling next week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 13:39:55 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>/2017/conference/2017/03/01/node-ctf-workshop.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2017/conference/2017/03/01/node-ctf-workshop.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>conference</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cut-off date to get a conference t-shirt</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Our tickets all come with a complimentary conference t-shirt or (our new option -
check your emails if you’d already selected a t-shirt and want to swap) a
canvas bag - but we need to get our order in to the printers soon. The last date
for you get your details to us and get your t-shirt or bag is &lt;strong&gt;this Sunday, the
26th of Feb, at midnight NZ time&lt;/strong&gt;. So if you’ve been waiting to buy your
ticket, or you have a ticket but you haven’t yet entered your details, you need
to get on that sharpish!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;javascript-nz-community-awards&quot;&gt;JavaScript NZ community awards&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the conference we’ll be voting on our first JS educator and JS contributer
award recepients - if you’d like to nominate someone for either of these awards
please see the details &lt;a href=&quot;http://javascript.org.nz/awards&quot;&gt;on the society website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;two-weeks-to-go&quot;&gt;Two weeks to go!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re now at &lt;strong&gt;less than 25 tickets remaining&lt;/strong&gt;, so now is a great time to &lt;a href=&quot;https://ti.to/javascript-nz/nz-js-con-2017&quot;&gt;get your ticket&lt;/a&gt; —
and don’t forget that we have a &lt;a href=&quot;/diversity-and-financial-aid-fund/&quot;&gt;Diversity and Financial Aid fund&lt;/a&gt; if you need help travelling to
the conference or getting a ticket.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 14:39:55 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>/2017/conference/2017/02/22/cutoff-date-for-t-shirts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2017/conference/2017/02/22/cutoff-date-for-t-shirts.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>conference</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NodeBots workshop</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In association with our good friends at &lt;a href=&quot;http://nodebots.co.nz/&quot;&gt;NodeBots NZ&lt;/a&gt;
we’re offering a workshop to conference attendees. The NodeBots team can help
you program a quadcopter, plus they have a plethora of other robots, hardware
and projects you can hack on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the Friday afternoon between lunch and afternoon tea the middle room will
hold the workshop, which can support up to 50 participants. Because of the
limited space &lt;strong&gt;we need conference attendees to register their spot&lt;/strong&gt; for the
workshop - ticket holders, please check your emails for an annoucement. If you
don’t have a ticket for the conference yet, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ti.to/javascript-nz/nz-js-con-2017&quot;&gt;sign up
now&lt;/a&gt; and then follow the link in
your ticket confirmation email for the workshop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;less-than-a-month-to-go&quot;&gt;Less than a month to go&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re now at &lt;strong&gt;less than 60 tickets remaining&lt;/strong&gt;, so now is a great time to &lt;a href=&quot;https://ti.to/javascript-nz/nz-js-con-2017&quot;&gt;get your ticket&lt;/a&gt; —
and don’t forget that we have a &lt;a href=&quot;/diversity-and-financial-aid-fund/&quot;&gt;Diversity and Financial Aid fund&lt;/a&gt; if you need help travelling to
the conference or getting a ticket.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 14:39:55 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>/2017/conference/2017/02/19/nodebots-workshop.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2017/conference/2017/02/19/nodebots-workshop.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>conference</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keynotes and schedule</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re very pleased to annouce the speaker lineup for the conference. First, our
keynote speakers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;raquel-vélez&quot;&gt;Raquel Vélez&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Raquel Vélez is the engineering manager of the services team at npm, Inc. in
Oakland, CA. She has previously worked at institutions such as Caltech, NASA
JPL, the MIT Lincoln Laboratory, and various universities in Europe. She is a
co-author of the book Make: JavaScript Robotics. In her off time, you can find
her baking, co-hosting the Reactive Podcast, and speaking. Also, hanging out
with her hilarious husband and two cats dressed in dog suits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;ri-liu&quot;&gt;Ri Liu&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Originally from Brisbane, Ri now lives in Melbourne after enjoying several years
in Chicago and San Francisco. She specialises in expressing data in novel ways
and exposing social injustices using data. She has worked for The Guardian,
creating data stories and interactive content, and has also worked on print,
experiential and digital projects for Google, Facebook, Foreign Affairs, The
Conversation, The Nation, Popular Science and Pew Charitable Trusts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;full-schedule&quot;&gt;Full schedule&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The full schedule is &lt;a href=&quot;/schedule/&quot;&gt;now up&lt;/a&gt;. Many thanks to
everyone who submitted, our paper review team had a tough time finalising the
lineup from the many excellent submissions we recieved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/schedule/&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary&quot;&gt;View schedule&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re now at &lt;strong&gt;a third of all our tickets&lt;/strong&gt; registered, so there has never been a
better time to &lt;a href=&quot;https://ti.to/javascript-nz/nz-js-con-2017&quot;&gt;get your ticket&lt;/a&gt; —
and don’t forget that we have a &lt;a href=&quot;/diversity-and-financial-aid-fund/&quot;&gt;Diversity and Financial Aid fund&lt;/a&gt; if you need help getting to
the conference.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 15:39:55 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>/2017/conference/2017/02/05/keynotes-and-schedule.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2017/conference/2017/02/05/keynotes-and-schedule.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>conference</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>CFP closes</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The call for papers has now closed — thank you to all our submitters, we’re very
grateful for your hard work. Our team of reviewers will be starting to go
through all the submissions this weekend, and we’ll be in touch with potential
speakers soon. We should be able to announce the full schedule for the
conference soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, don’t forget that you can &lt;a href=&quot;https://ti.to/javascript-nz/nz-js-con-2017&quot;&gt;now buy
tickets&lt;/a&gt; and that we have a
&lt;a href=&quot;/conference/update/tickets/2017/01/17/diversity-and-financial-aid.html&quot;&gt;Diversity and Financial Aid fund&lt;/a&gt; if you
need help getting to the conference.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 11:39:55 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>/2017/conference/cfp/2017/01/27/cfp-closes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2017/conference/cfp/2017/01/27/cfp-closes.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>conference</category>
        
        <category>cfp</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>CFP extended until 27th January</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In honour of the fact that it’s long weekend here in Wellington we’re extending the call for papers (talk submissions) ever-so-slightly to this Friday, the 27th of January, at 9pm. So there has never been a better time to get your proposal in!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Last%20week%20to%20submit%20a%20talk%20to%20nz.js(con)%3B%20http%3A%2F%2Fconference.javascript.org.nz%2F%20%23nzjscon%20%23jsnz%20%23javascript%20%23nz&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;icon icon--twitter&quot;&gt;&lt;svg viewBox=&quot;0 0 16 16&quot; width=&quot;16px&quot; height=&quot;16px&quot;&gt;&lt;path fill=&quot;#828282&quot; d=&quot;M15.969,3.058c-0.586,0.26-1.217,0.436-1.878,0.515c0.675-0.405,1.194-1.045,1.438-1.809c-0.632,0.375-1.332,0.647-2.076,0.793c-0.596-0.636-1.446-1.033-2.387-1.033c-1.806,0-3.27,1.464-3.27,3.27 c0,0.256,0.029,0.506,0.085,0.745C5.163,5.404,2.753,4.102,1.14,2.124C0.859,2.607,0.698,3.168,0.698,3.767 c0,1.134,0.577,2.135,1.455,2.722C1.616,6.472,1.112,6.325,0.671,6.08c0,0.014,0,0.027,0,0.041c0,1.584,1.127,2.906,2.623,3.206 C3.02,9.402,2.731,9.442,2.433,9.442c-0.211,0-0.416-0.021-0.615-0.059c0.416,1.299,1.624,2.245,3.055,2.271 c-1.119,0.877-2.529,1.4-4.061,1.4c-0.264,0-0.524-0.015-0.78-0.046c1.447,0.928,3.166,1.469,5.013,1.469 c6.015,0,9.304-4.983,9.304-9.304c0-0.142-0.003-0.283-0.009-0.423C14.976,4.29,15.531,3.714,15.969,3.058z&quot;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;Tweet about the CFP closing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget that we have a Diversity and Financial Aid fund, which can give you a helping hand if you want to speak but you’re not sure if you can afford to attend. You can read more about it &lt;a href=&quot;/conference/update/tickets/2017/01/17/diversity-and-financial-aid.html&quot;&gt;over here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other news, we’re pretty busy here at &lt;strong&gt;nz.js(con); hq&lt;/strong&gt; - ticket sales are rolling in, we’re sorting the designs for our t-shirts and stickers, and our keynote speakers will be announced soon! &lt;a href=&quot;https://ti.to/javascript-nz/nz-js-con-2017&quot;&gt;Buy your ticket now&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 11:39:55 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>/2017/conference/cfp/2017/01/21/cfp-extended-until-27th-jan.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2017/conference/cfp/2017/01/21/cfp-extended-until-27th-jan.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>conference</category>
        
        <category>cfp</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
